

MUHAMMAD HARIS

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

03093185997

OHA Karachi , Pakistan

EDUCATION

2021 - PRESENT
MEHRAN UNIVERSITY OF
ENGINEERING AND
TECHNOLOGY

• Software Engineering

2019 - 2021 THE CITY HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL

• Intermediate

SKILLS

- JAVA
- C++
- html
- CSS
- Java Script
- Type Script
- React js
- Next js
- UI / UX

LANGUAGES

- English (Very Good Command)
- Urdu (Native Speaker)
- Sindhi (Native Speaker)

PROFILE

A Software Engineering student at Mehran University, specialized in Web Development with a keen focus on creating responsive and User-friendly Web applications. Proficient in HTML, CSS , JavaScript, React, Type Script and modern web development techniques.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Magsad Private Limited

JUNE, 2024 - AUG, 2024

Software Engineering Intern

 During internship, I actively participated in Web Development tasks, I do my best for creating responsive designs and fullfilling daily assignments which is assigned by the team lead.

MLSA MUET Khairpur

MAR, 2023 - DEC, 2023

Lead Finance

 In my role as Lead Finance at MLSA MUET KHAIRPUR, I acquired skills in effectively managing sponsorship funds.

Magsad Private Limited

AUG, 2022 - JULY, 2023

Software Engineering Intern

 During my internship, I actively participated in Quality Assurance tasks, ensuring the smooth functioning of web development projects by fulfilling daily assignments delegated by the team lead.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Netflix Clone

GitHub:

https://github.com/MuhammadHarisBaloch/Netflix-Clone

Dwello-Web

GitHub:

https://github.com/MuhammadHarisBaloch/Dwello-Web

Scoot-App

GitHub:

https://github.com/MuhammadHarisBaloch/Scoot-App

Bella-Olonje

GitHub:

https://github.com/MuhammadHarisBaloch/Bella-Olonje